Okay, this Welcome to Haldi's WhatsApp
name is Dev, in today's video we are going to talk
about health
insurance, yes, I have personally been using
this company's health insurance for many years, I have
clicked three-four times, so
whatever my
experience is here, I am going to share it with you guys
here, so guys, this
is not a sponsored video, you can watch it,
I will show you my policy here,
you can write that I have a proper policy, that is, I did
not reduce the care,
and I have clicked here many times, so
here today I am going to talk
about all the pros and cons of this company,
along with this, a new
plan has been launched in the name of Classic John
and you can see it on the top of the policy market also
and it seems to be a very good
plan, so I thought that I should
discuss it with you guys here because
its free plan is quite low, as compared to the
company, so guys, now let us
talk about the clearance, this is a very old
shortcoming, first I  It was called Religare.
It was started in July 2012
and in 2021, it launched its own branding in the
name of Ali's Engineers. If we
talk about guys, then this is a kid company which deals only in
health insurance services.
Just Like A Star Health
Insurance has grown in the city. If we talk about data, then
in terms of data, it is far
ahead of many other health insurance companies.
If we talk about its market share, then it has a
market share of more than five percent, which is almost the same here.
Such Egg or ICC has become taller. Such clothes
also have around the same amount. So
guys, as I told you, there is
no sponsored video, so whatever I am telling you here,
whatever I am telling you the good things, whatever
I am telling you the bad things, all of it is based on
my experience. I
talk to you with great love in the morning
that after all, we should use
this humorous poet instead of other health insurance companies. So
see, I did a lot of research here first
and I
Whatever experience I have had, even if it is
Star Haldi, here is the policy of the juice company,
before that I have done such and
ICC's growth, so my
best digital experience is here
with Clear Haldi Josh, you can
check its total or get your mobile repaired,
now through the simple login process, as after
logging in, all your policy
documents appear in front of you, you can
book an appointment for your health checkup, you
can keep all your health there, if you want to click then
you can also clean online or do history, you
can upload all your documents, that is, Hero has given all the facilities in a very
easy way on its web portal and that is for
you, apart from this, if we talk about the
claim settlement in this, then
95% of the claims are settled, if we
talk about Vitamin D in Nagar, then
70% of the claims are settled in the state, hey, what
I told you about it is a
new plan for the benefit of adding classic,
what is the special thing about this plan, these people have given ISRO  The
device is divided into three zones, like on the
strength of Mumbai, then all the metro
cities have been combined, both
Bengaluru, Pune, Nashik, all this has happened and whatever is
added on the earth, then what have we done here, whatever will
come for free will
come here zone wise, it means if you
assume that it is like a city which is not a
metro city, then your free will is
very useful, talk about Jaipur JCT in this planet,
where Malik, when I introduce myself
as twenty years old and plus, after reaching the office, I
add here, then there is a
premium on vegetables of Birauli 10,492, which means almost it has happened
in the employment development officer,
which is my heart health worth Rs 5 lakh, and
this is what I will make a comeback at home with
Star Health, if with any other deficiency, then
this is my health issues, they
come around 10011-12000,
now if I tell you its USP, then first of all your
free will automatically get reduced here, this is on
your city in which
you also live here, but you this  Don't
think that my cover is like that of the same city
or you can click here anywhere in all India.
Apart from this, if I
talk about OPD only, then here you
get the option of addition of OPD cover,
but for this there is a slide break, so
they will have to be done. What does OPD cover mean,
suppose what is general health
insurance, you can click and
talk when you are admitted in the hospital,
but if you are a
physical person, we basically go to the doctor, take
any consultation, get life reports done,
here suppose there is
no need to get admitted in the hospital, then
you are not able to cover the health issues there,
but if you take this OPD work
option, you have to play a little slide and another
₹3000 mixture, but in this this
thing gets curved here, there is a
sweater limit for this person,
so OPD only
works like an add-on here, if
I talk about room rent, ICU charges, then
here  You get a signal private room, there is
any traffic limit
like Star Halke, Tabo Saiyan, three nights, up to
₹5 lakh, you
can change your look here, so whatever
you get here, there is no fee on the
look, there is no AC charge, there is also
coverage for erasing the evidence of yours, the good thing is whether it is home
or hospital, both
get coverage here, along with this, guys this option
is wrong, the research of unlimited restoration
means that if you
click on multi for a year, then you will
not have any nightmare, Bali ji, first you clicked your
clip of 5 lakh in this year,
now the entire 5 lakh is spent,
now if you click once on the same village, then the
5 lakh which has been spent of yours gets
restored here, against this,
if I talk about no claim bonus, then
yours keeps increasing from time to time,
if you do not do it in any previous year
and it goes up to a maximum of 150 percent,
meaning  That is, if you have taken ₹5 for your turmeric
powder and never
play it for the whole year, then
this ₹2565 will keep increasing every year and the
date of extension can increase till the end.
Along with this, you
get a free health checkup for one year for yourself and for
all your family members. You would
also be getting your benefits here along
with roti, so you can book an appointment on their app or
website
and get your Excel health checkup done for
free there, so
this is a one-time help, it is not that
you will get it again and again, meaning
you will get help only once a year. After this,
if you have any existing disease and at
that time you are taking health insurance here, then the
waiting period here is
minimum 4 years. If
you
want to click for this, then you will have to wait here for four years.
Apart from this, you can also talk to the
General Physician on the Zindagi mobile app.  You
can talk on 121 call normally, in
fact, a general MBBS doctor wakes up and the
same PIN is available to you, so if
you have any special problems like cold, cough etc., which
means it is a normal thing, then you
can directly take a concentration on their portal, plus on the app,
apart from this, there is a free voicemail
address here, after this, you get a cover of 7 days before and proportion of
90s on many occasions, that is,
whenever you get admitted in the hospital,
it provides you with a 60-day cover before and after that, a cover of 9 days after discharge from the hospital,
how did you know, it
includes day treatment and hospital
collection nutrition, suppose what happens many times,
like the cost was capped, beds were
not available in the hospital, then
treatment would have been done at home, so these things are also
included here, apart from this,
if there is any cataract, it is covered here,
but now a limit will be imposed based on ₹40,
explain.  You can say that if you have a
health insurance of 15 lakh rupees, I will talk about
what is not covered in it, so
see, while I am talking about maternity cover, it
means that
you cannot comment on pregnancy related issues in it, you
can not make any claim for it, whereas
what is there in other policies, they give you a minimum meeting,
that is, you have to create a meeting for 2 years,
after that, if you
go for net related special within 30 years, then you
can click on this note here, how can you know that
the World Wide Awake is not available here, that is, if you
want to give you medical treatment outside India, then
this thing is not available here,
you do not get the obscene dance of Delhi here,
as if you are admitted in the hospital, then what does the
company do, it
unites against Delhi in its plans, this means that here
you will get health tips,
all your hospital expenses will be borne by the
company here, but you will have to bear the expenses on daily basis, that is, the
expenses of travel are good.  The
expenses incurred on food and drinks,
these things are not provided to your family members here, like
I told you that this city wise, here
your free cutting of your clothes, along with this, is covered
under additional cover in which sister and health
checkup are covered instantly, but it is
around ₹3000, yes 5,000, whatever you
should review, now you can see that there is an extra expense on two to three or
four, but keep in
mind that if you add this on both sides, then there is a
cutting limit, what does it mean,
just assume up to ₹5000, the
PTK that you go to with a general hospital can be covered on this,
see, only ₹2000, you will be
able to cover this here, so according to me, these
four are not very beneficial,
this is an optional feature, if you want to take it, you
can take it again and again and if you have to take the patient to the hospital for
normal checkup to
consult a normal doctor, then only
you should add it, otherwise it will be covered from inside immediately  I can only
see it above my hotel.
If I want to book an appointment with any service center here, I
want to start anywhere in
Life, or I want to download my report card, or I
want to show it to any other committee, then
all the facilities are available here, you can get it on the portal,
you don't need to go anywhere,
otherwise mostly we keep getting calls from the call center
and sometimes the call does
n't work or there is a time
backup in case of emergency, so here is a good
facility that you can reset
your clean here yourself through the mobile app of Izzat,
along with that
you can upload your clean documents there
online, whereas
if I talk about photos, there are a lot of problems there, you are
not able to upload them properly, whereas from this
one you can say that the daughter of this portal looks
quite amazing to me, so this was it, in this I
told you both the adult and who are the
care health insurance company, you slept
suicide this video, if you people at all  If you have any doubts,
please tell me in the comment section.
Thank you guys, thank you.